字幕组
ZiMuZu.tv
原创翻译  双语字幕
最快首发美剧日剧下载请登录
字幕组网站www.ZiMuZu.tv
翻译：王大可 Reginamoon 小暴徒 想名字好难 JonnyG 木浅薰 Timothy
翻译：dzysteven 某羽 kahiko  校对：油炸电风扇   木浅薰
时间轴：壬虚浪影  今
后期：斯人      总监：某羽
诉 讼 双 雄
第六季   第四集
《诉讼双雄》前情提要
Previously on "Suits"...
瑞秋  我是邓巴教授
Rachel, it's Professor Dunbar.
我在想你是否对
I was wondering if you'd be interested in helping me
无罪计划感兴趣
with the Innocence Project.
你想让我帮你让无辜的人摆脱死刑
You want me to help you get an innocent man off death row?
什么事  哈维
What do you want, Harvey?
帮我保护迈克・罗斯
Help me protect Mike Ross.
他和我抓的一个人被关在一起
He's in there with a guy I put away,
那人可不是吃素的
and the guy is no joke.
但你要我做什么
What am I supposed to do?
我要你把那个人转到别的监狱
You're supposed to move the guy to another prison.
你想跟我一对一  来吧
You want me one-on-one? You got it.
我打算用这个  而他们会按住你
I'm gonna use this, and they're gonna hold you.
-不不不  -怎么回事
- No! - What's going on here?
你为什么带警卫一起回来
Why'd you come back with a guard?
我那么做不是为了让你原谅我
I didn't do it to get you to forgive me.
我当初就不该让他进来
I never should have let him in here in the first place.
你在等待审判期间在监狱服刑的时间
The time you served while awaiting trial
没有被算入刑期
was never factored into your sentence.
再过六周你就能被保释了
You're eligible for parole in six weeks.
你以为我不知道这是你的保护人
You think I don't know this is your protector's idea
用来保护你的把戏吗
to get me off your back?
不  弗兰克
Nah, Frank.
哈维想的办法是让我告诉这些人你做了线人
Harvey's idea was for me to tell these guys that you're an informant.
我找到了让迈克提前出狱的办法
I figured out a way to get Mike out early.
代价是什么
What's the catch?
他得告发他的室友
He has to inform on his roommate.
迈克让他开口就自由了
Mike gets him to turn, he's free.
你们什么时候要迈克的答案
When do you need an answer by?
昨天
Yesterday.
而且答案必须是接受
And the answer needs to be yes.
哈维  等等
Harvey, wait a second.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
你觉得我要去哪
Where do you think I'm going?
我要去见迈克
I'm gonna see Mike.
我知道你要说什么
And I know what you're going to say,
但迈克是为了保护我们进监狱
but Mike went to prison so we wouldn't have to,
现在他因为一个我送进去的人身陷危险
and now he's in danger from a guy I put away.
所以请理解我不能
So you'll forgive me if I don't stand around and wait
干等着你来拍板
for you to drop the hammer.
你以为我愿意让他在里面呆着吗
You think I like the idea of him rotting in that place?
但如果你想办好这事
But if you want this thing to work,
就不能大半夜的跑过去
you can't go running up there in the middle of the night.
你听到卡荷尔的话了  他要尽快答复
You heard Cahill. He needs an answer yesterday.
他需要的是结果
What he needs is results.
如果迈克的律师在大半夜的
And if Mike's lawyer pulls him out of his cell
把他从牢房里叫出来
in the middle of the night, then his roommate
那这事还没开始张罗
is going to sense there's something wrong
他室友就能察觉出有问题
before this thing even gets started.
好吧  但我明早第一时间就要赶过去
Fine, but I'm going up there first thing in the morning,
你说什么都阻止不了我
and nothing you say is going to stop me.
睡不着吗
Can't sleep?
也不算是
Not really.
好吧  反正你也醒着
Well, as long as you're up,
不如考虑一下放点自己的照片吧
might want to think about putting up some pictures of your own
这样你就不用总盯着我的看了
that way yon won't have to keep staring at mine.
他们多大
How old are they?
麦蒂七岁了
Maddy is seven.
纳特刚刚五岁
Nate just turned five.
他们看起来很可爱
They look really sweet.
是啊  他们很棒
Yeah...they're great.
你多久能见一次他们
How often do you get to see 'em?
-不见  -什么叫不见
- I don't. - What do you mean you don't?
离婚闹僵了还是什么别的事
Bad divorce or something?
不  不是那样
Nah, nah, nothing like that.
我们结婚十年了
We've been married for ten years.
我只是不让他们来这里
I just--I just don't let 'em come here.
什么  为什么
What? Why not?
他们不应该看到自己的父亲是个罪犯
They shouldn't see their father as a criminal.
凯文  别这样伙计
Kevin, come on, man.
我知道这对他们来讲很难
I know it's hard on them.
在这里的每一天我都很痛苦
It tears me up every single day that I'm here.
但他们是孩子  他们很顽强
But they're kids. They're resilient.
是吗  我不太确定
Yeah, I wouldn't be so sure.
迈克  你没有孩子
Well, Mike, you don't have kids.
你理解不了
So you don't know.
我确实没有
No. I don't.
但我知道孩子思念父亲是什么感觉
But I do know what it's like to be a kid missing his dad.
别跟我说你的父亲抛弃了家庭
Please don't tell me your old man abandoned the family.
在我11岁的时候我的双亲都死于了车祸
Both of my parents died in a car accident when I was 11.
肇事的司机喝醉了
Hit by a drunk driver.
天哪  对不起  迈克
Jesus, that's... I'm sorry, Mike.
是啊  那是很久以前的事了
Yeah, it was a long time ago.
凯文  我理解你保护孩子的本能
Kevin, I understand the instinct to protect your children,
但你在保护他们什么呢
but what are you protecting them from?
你什么意思
What do you mean?
我的意思是我们做室友也有段时间了
I mean we've been roommates for a while now.
你不认为也该说说你是为什么进来的吗
Don't you think it's time you told me what you're in here for?
罗斯
Hey, Ross.
你的律师来了
Your lawyer's here.
-现在  -我只是来传个话
- Now? - I'm just the messenger.
你到底出不出来
You want out of this box or not?
贝利先生  我是瑞秋・赞恩
Mr. Bailey, my name is Rachel Zane.
我是哥伦比亚大学法学院的一名学生
I am a law student at Columbia,
我是来和你谈谈你的案子的
and I'm here to talk to you about your case.
学生
Student?
是的  我在负责协助无罪计划
Yes, we work alongside the Innocence Project
决定你的情况是否适合进行上诉
to determine if you have the criteria for an appeal.
你知道我被宣判死刑多久了吗
Do you know how long I've been sittin' on death row?
12年  我读过你的档案
12 years. I read your file.
最近的十年中  我一直在写信
And for the last ten of 'em, I've been writing letters
想找一个愿意听我故事的律师
and begging any lawyer to listen to my story.
他们终于考虑回应我了
And they finally get around to getting back to me,
却都不能出于礼貌的
and they don't even have the courtesy
派个真正的律师来吗
of sendin' me a real lawyer?
贝利先生  相信我  我会为你尽力争取的
Mr. Bailey, trust me, I will fight for you.
你是个学生
You're a student.
你屁都帮不了
You can't do shit for me.
我告诉你  你非常冷血地
Well, you know what? You killed two people.
杀了两个人
In cold blood.
你心知肚明  我也一样
You know it, and I know it,
那也正是你进监狱的原因
and that's why you're in there,
所以谢谢你让我决定
so thank you for making the decision
不把你的案子想得太简单
to not take your case an easy one.
你不了解我
You don't know me.
你所知道的不过是从一些破文件上读来的东西
All you know is what you read in some damn file.
我没杀人
I didn't kill anyone.
这句话我说了12年了
I've been saying it for 12 years
而且我也可以证明
and I can prove it.
你说得对  我不认识你
You're right. I don't know you.
但你也同样不认识我
And you don't know me either.
所以你到底要不要给彼此一个机会
So do you want to take a chance on each other or not?
我需要帮助  赞恩女士
I need help, Ms. Zane.
那就让我来帮你
So let me help you.
哈维  你来这里做什么
Harvey, what are you doing here?
我需要和你谈件事
There's something I need to talk to you about.
坐下
Sit down.
什么事
What is it?
肖恩・卡荷尔刚刚来找了我
I just got a visit from Sean Cahill.
关于加洛的事吗
About Gallo?
你不是说他没办法把他转到其他监狱去吗
I thought you said he can't get him transferred.
的确不能  但后来他发现
He can't, but it turns out
他有办法把你弄出来
there's a way he can get you out.
"出来"是什么意思
What do you mean "out"?
"出来"就是
I mean out,
你可以走出那扇大门
as in you walk out that front door
永远不再回头
and you never look back.
-条件是什么  -迈克...
- What's the catch? - Mike--
哈维  要不是有其他什么条件
Harvey, you're not here telling me that I can get out
你是不会带着那副表情
with that look on your face
来通知我能出去的
if there isn't something else.
他需要你举报你的狱友
He needs you to inform on your cellmate.
什么
What?
假如你套出什么信息能使得他岳父被定罪
If whatever you get leads to a conviction on his father-in-law,
他就会帮你减刑  然后你就可以出来了
he'll commute your sentence and you get to walk.
那家伙干了什么
What'd the guy do?
谁在乎他干了什么啊
Who cares what he did?
我在乎  因为要不是事情很糟糕
I care, because if it was so bad,
凯文一开始就会供出他了
why didn't Kevin turn on him in the first place?
迈克  那又有什么关系呢
Mike, what does it matter?
他能把你弄出去
He can get you out.
他是我在这里唯一的朋友
This is my only friend in here.
我是不会背叛他的
I'm not gonna betray him.
朋友  妈的  听我说
Friend? Listen to me, God damn it.
这里有个人正想办法杀你
There's someone in here trying to kill you
而我正你一个出去的机会
and I'm giving you a way out.
我正在处理加洛了
I'm taking care of Gallo.
那他妈又是什么意思
What the hell is that supposed to mean?
意思是我做了你叫我做的事
It means that I did what you told me to do.
我威胁他说我要告诉大家他是个告密者
I threatened to tell people that he was an informant,
但与此同时我还帮他想了个办法获得假释
but what I also did was found out a way to get him parole.
假释  你疯了吗
Parole? Are you crazy?
他不可能获得假释的
He's not gonna get parole.
谁会批准啊
Who's gonna say he deserves it?
你知道吗  哈维
You know what, Harvey?
与其因为加洛不可能假释
Instead of coming here and telling me to betray my cellmate
就来这里让我背叛我的狱友
because Gallo will never get parole,
也许你更应该帮我让他获得假释
maybe you should be helping me get it for him.
我绝对不会帮那个人渣干任何事情的
I'm never helping that piece of shit do anything,
而且这件事和加洛无关  你是知道的
and this isn't about Gallo and you know it.
的确  这事关你叫我背叛一个我信任的人
No, it's about you telling me to turn on the one guy in here that I trust
就因为卡荷尔提出了一个
based on some plan that Cahill has
我们都不知道行不行得通的计划
that we don't even know will work.
不  迈克
No, Mike.
这事关给你一个机会  重获你
It's about giving you a chance to get your life back
现在还没什么大变化的生活
while it still looks the same.
你到底要不要接受这个条件
Now, are you going to take it or not?
妈的  西梅汁事件又重演了
Son of a bitch, it's the prune juice all over again.
搞什么
What the?
蠢蛋
Hey, douche stick.
是不是你把我的马克杯拿到这里来的
Are you responsible for my mugs being here?
我之前没有...我没有...
I didn't--I don't--
我们没有其他东西可用了
we didn't have anything else to use.
我不管
I don't give a shit!
把这些杯子放回...
Take those things and put 'em back where--
瞧瞧  这不是路易・屎特嘛
Well, if it isn't Louis Shit.
-发生什么事了  老大  -你个混蛋
- What's happening, boss? - You bastard.
你拿了我的马克杯
You took my mugs,
却连亲自动手的胆量都没有
and you didn't even have the balls to do it yourself.
我完全不知道您在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about,
但假如您的东西出现在了这里
but if something of yours is in here,
那和我完全没关系
it had nothing to do with me.
是吗  你为什么不问问这个结巴小丑
Really? Why don't you ask the stuttering ass clown?
我们需要用它们来做我们的...
We needed them for our...
尿检
urine tests.
你刚刚说什么
What'd you say?
你们在我的妙语马克杯里撒尿了
You peed on my catch phrase?
我不知道哪个更搞笑些
I don't know what's funnier--
是你有"妙语"还是我们在里面撒尿了
you got a catch phrase or that we peed on it.
把那些马克杯给我拿去消毒然后销毁
I want those mugs sterilized and I want 'em destroyed.
它们是你的马克杯  你想干啥都行
They're your mugs, you do what you want,
但我打死也不会碰它们的
but I'm not touching 'em with a ten-foot pole.
你知道鲁特曼有多爱吃芦笋吗
You know how much asparagus Luterman eats?
回见  老大
Later, Chief.
今早情况如何
How'd it go this morning?
我被震惊了
I was petrified.
那可是死刑  震惊就对了
Death row. How could you not be?
不止是这个
It's not just that.
到那里的时候  我忽然发现
When I got there, it hit me
假如我接了这个案子
that if I do this,
有一条人命就被握在我手上了
I have a man's life in my hands.
瑞秋  你可以搞定的
Rachel, you can handle it.
我知道我可以
I know I can.
那我为什么感觉你正在为某事烦恼
Then why do I get the feeling that something is bothering you?
因为从那里回来时
Because when I got back from there,
我对那个可怜人的遭遇深感愤怒
I was so angry about what happened to that poor man
所以我坐下  开始办这个案子
that I sat down, I started working on this case,
然后我...我就没动过
and I-- I haven't moved since.
我不明白  这有什么不好的
I don't understand. Why is that bad?
因为这是自迈克离开后
Because it's the first time since Mike left
我第一次没有每分每秒都想着他
that I haven't thought about him every second.
听我说
Listen to me.
这是个好事
That's a good thing.
可我感觉不像是个好事
It doesn't feel like a good thing.
瑞秋  你不能一辈子都活得如坐针毡
Rachel, you can't live your life on pins and needles.
这对你不好
It's not healthy for you.
对迈克也不好  对任何人都不好
It's not healthy for Mike. It's not healthy for anyone.
忘了他就好了吗
And forgetting about him is healthy?
这难道不是你接这个案子的原因吗
Isn't that why you took this case?
来转移你的注意力
To give yourself something to focus on?
-没错  但我  -既然如此就别抗拒
- Yes, but I just-- - Then don't fight it.
如果投入到一个释放无辜人的案子中
If working to free an innocent man helps you
能让你忘了迈克一会
to forget about Mike for a while,
他一定第一个告诉你应该这么做
he would be the first person to tell you to do it.
相信我
And trust me,
如果你真能沉浸在这个案子里
if you really lose yourself in this,
我觉得等迈克出来的时间感觉起来
I have a feeling it's gonna seem like a lot less than two years
会比两年短多了
before he gets out.
哈维在哪
Where's Harvey?
他不在办公室
Harvey's not here.
那就赶紧叫他回来
Well, get his ass in here
因为他和那群商人私下达成了交易
because he made some goddamn side deal
而我现在想让他们赶紧滚
with those traders and I want them out.
路易  我告诉你  现在不是时候
Louis, I am telling you, now is not the time.
那我告诉你  我受不了再多看一天
And I am telling you that I cannot look at
他们那些丑陋愚蠢的脸了
their smug, stupid faces for one more day.
也许你不用看
Maybe you don't have to look at them.
你什么意思
What are you talking about?
路易  我告诉过你
Louis, did I ever tell you
-我在纽约住的第一套公寓吗  -没有
- about my first apartment in the city? - No.
我和别人合租一个37平米的单间公寓
I was sharing a 400 square-foot studio
那简直是个噩梦  直到我们决定
and it was a disaster until we finally decided
隔开房间保留隐私才好一些
that we had to separate our spaces for privacy.
这可不是《布雷迪家庭》  唐娜
Well, this isn't "The Brady Bunch," Donna.
我们不可能在办公室中央画一个三八线
We can't put a masking tape line down the center of the office.
我不是说让你画三八线  路易
I'm not talking about masking tape, Louis.
我是想说雇一个建筑师
I am talking about hiring an architect
重新规划办公室布局
to reconfigure the offices.
你说得太对了
You're right!
我们甚至可以重新装修
We can even do a remodel,
这是我过去五年里一直想做的
which is what I've been wanting to do for the last five years.
最重要的是  你不用再和
And the best part is, you don't have to deal with
那些混蛋商人打交道了
those asshole traders ever again.
-唐娜你简直是个天才  -我知道
- Donna, you're a genius. - I know.
午饭之前给我六个建筑师的名字
Get me the names of six architects before lunch.
路易  你有自己的秘书
Louis, you have your own secretary.
谢谢你这么没用
Thanks for nothing.
我图个什么
Why do I even?
你可算来了
Nice of you to show up.
这些土豆都是我一个人削的
Been peeling these potatoes by myself.
对不起  我刚才有事
Sorry, I...got caught up.
对了  你和你律师谈得如何
Speaking of which, how'd it go with your lawyer?
你要出去了吗
You gettin' out of here?
什么
What?
我开玩笑的  有什么事吗
I'm just kidding. So what's going on?
没什么
Nothing.
不重要
It's not important.
你律师来你都不知道
Your lawyer shows up without you knowing about it
这事还能不重要吗
and it's not important?
拜托  你以为我是三岁小孩
Come on, do I look like I was born yesterday?
我说了不重要
I just said it is not important.
对不起我留你一个人在这干活
And I'm sorry I left you hanging,
但要不是我你都没有这份工作
but you wouldn't even have this job without me.
要不是因为你我也不需要工作
I wouldn't even need this job if it weren't for you.
你到底怎么了
So what's your problem?
对不起  凯文  我...
I'm sorry, Kevin, I'm...
我今天过得不顺
I'm just not having a good day.
没事
Hey, it's okay.
别担心  好吗
Don't sweat it. All right?
反正这事与我无关
I mean, it's none of my business anyway.
不  其实  和你有关
No, actually, it is your business.
他来告诉我他想过办法让加洛转监狱
He came here to tell me that he tried to get Gallo transferred,
但...看来不可能了
but...it's not gonna happen.
只要咱俩统一战线
Well, as long as we stick together,
我们也能对付加洛  对吧
we can deal with Gallo anyway, right?
对  我就是这么跟哈维说的
Yeah, that's-- that's what I told Harvey.
好吧
Right.
下次再见到他  替我跟他说谢谢他的努力
Next time you talk to him, tell him I said thanks for trying.
怎么样
How'd it go?
他说他要考虑一下
He said he had to think about it.
什么  为什么
What? Why?
因为他愚蠢至极
'Cause he's an idiot, that's why.
那你接下来要怎么办
So what're you gonna do?
我要想办法争取点时间
I'm gonna figure out how to buy us some time.
那你最好快点想  因为卡荷尔在你办公室
Well, you better do it fast because Cahill's in your office
他等着答复
and he wants an answer.
肖恩
Sean.
他怎么说
What'd he say?
他说想看到详细的书面文件
Said he wants to see the details in writing.
我没这闲情逸致  哈维
I'm not in the mood, Harvey.
我也没在瞎说
And I'm not messing around.
快告诉我你是开玩笑的
Please tell me you're kidding me.
拜托  简直扯淡
Oh, come on, this is bullshit.
你知道我说话算数的
You know my word is good.
我知道  我就是这么告诉他的
Yeah, and I told him that,
但他不想冒着背腹受敌的风险
and he doesn't want to risk putting a target on his back
最后却发现所谓减刑
and then find out commuting his sentence
真的只是减了一半刑期而已
really means cutting it in half.
他不用承担任何风险
He's not risking anything.
没人会发现
No one's gonna find out.
我敢说弗兰克・加洛之前也是这么想的
I'm sure that's exactly what Frank Gallo thought.
要么你拿来书面文件  要么这事就没戏了
So either put it in writing or we don't have a deal.
他不同意  对不对
He didn't go for it, did he?
你什么意思
What are you talking about?
迈克承不承担风险和
Mike being at risk has nothing to do
书面文件毫无关系
with putting anything in writing.
而且你告诉过我他不会同意的
And you told me he wouldn't go for it,
哈维  跟我说实话吧
so Harvey... tell me the truth.
好吧  他拒绝了
All right, he said no.
但是肖恩  我跟你说  他会回心转意的
But Sean, I'm telling you, he'll come around.
他只是需要几天时间考虑
He just needs a couple of days.
你知道为了让这件事开始进行
Do you know how many strings I pulled
我找了多少关系吗
to put this thing in motion?
我所知道的是  如果这个案子对你来说
What I know is, you wouldn't have pulled anything
不是非常重要你根本不会去找关系
if this case wasn't huge for you.
所以与其因为我说这还需要几天时间
So instead of yelling at me
就对我大吼大叫
for saying that it's gonna take a couple days,
你还不如痛快地给我几天时间
why don't you just give me a couple of days?
好的  哈维
Okay, Harvey.
协议依然有效
The deal's still on the table.
但如果我找到无需他的帮助也能继续的办法
But if I find a way to move forward without his help,
那协议立刻作废  他就要坐满两年牢了
there is no deal and he does the whole two years.
杰西卡
Jessica.
哈维
Harvey.
迈克怎么样了
What's going on with Mike?
我把卡荷尔的提议告诉他了
I gave him Cahill's offer.
他在考虑吗
And he's thinking about it?
我还在努力
I'm working on it.
在此期间  你不在的时候
Well, in the meantime, while you were out,
我接到了一通来自南森・巴恩斯的电话
I got a call from Nathan Burns.
他觉得有人正试图接管他的公司
He thinks someone's trying to take over his company.
他为什么会这么想
Why the hell would he think of that?
因为坊间传言称
Because word on the street is,
某人正在抛售一批他的股票
someone's selling off a block of his stock.
这完全说不通啊
That doesn't make sense.
我们从他那把萨特持有的股份买过来了
We bought Sutter's shares from him.
那些该死的交易员们
Those goddamn traders.
不可能
No way.
他们不会在不知会我的情况下这么做的
They wouldn't do that without telling me.
他们是很有诚信的买下来的
They bought it in good faith.
那么他们现在就是在很没诚信的抛售了
Well, they're dumping it in bad faith.
-这事我来处理  -不
- I'll take care of it-- - No.
你专心处理迈克的事情
You have your hands full with Mike.
这事我能搞定
I can handle this.
杰西卡  让他们加入进来是我的主意
Jessica, it was my idea to involve them.
应该由我来收拾残局
I should be the one to take care of it.
我不在乎那是谁的主意  哈维
I don't care whose idea it was, Harvey.
你把迈克的事情处理好
You take care of Mike.
喂
Hello?
丹伯里联邦监狱有人向你致电
You have a call from Danbury Federal Prison.
-你愿意承担费用吗  -愿意
- Do you accept the charges? - Yes, of course.
迈克  一切安好吗
Mike, is everything okay?
是的  是的  一切都好
Yeah. Yeah, everything's fine.
我只是想你了
I was just thinking about you.
我也在想你
I was thinking about you too.
你也是吗
You were?
是的  实际上  我刚正在和你进行
Yes, in fact, I was just in the middle
一场关于死刑上诉案的
of a heated discussion with you
最佳解决方案的热烈讨论之中
about the best way to handle a death row appeal.
我不大明白
I don't understand.
我接受了"无罪计划"的案子
I took on an Innocence Project case,
就想找点事做把心思从我们这一团乱麻中移开
just to have something to take my mind off of our troubles.
但是我  我不想把心思从你身上移开
But I...I didn't want to take my mind off of you.
所以我决定想象和你一起解决这个案子
So I figured I would just imagine we were working on it together.
我都不知道该说些什么了
I don't know what to say.
说你愿意加入
Say you're in.
我是说  那取决于我们决定采用什么样的策略
I mean, that depends on what strategy we landed on.
迈克  说真的  出了什么事吗
Mike, seriously, is there something wrong?
不  我只是想确保你一切安好
No, I just wanted to make sure you were doing okay.
还有  我们的感情依然没变
And that... that we were still good.
现在我有一件事可以让我不想我们的窘境
Now that I have something to take my mind off our situation
并且同时还能把我俩联系在一起
and connect me to you at the same time,
是的  我们的感情更好了
yeah, we're better than good.
好了  你能帮我转一下唐娜的分机吗
All right, can you do me a favor and transfer me to Donna?
当然  我能问下为什么吗
Of course. Can I ask why?
我只能打一个电话
I only get one phone call,
而我非常确定你这个想象我们一起
and I'm pretty sure she had something to do
工作的点子她有一份功劳
with the idea of you imagining us working together,
所以我想谢谢她
so I just want to thank her.
好的  我爱你
Okay. I love you.
我也爱你
I love you too.
喂
Hello?
唐娜  迈克在线上
Donna, I have Mike on the phone.
接过来
Put him through.
-喂  -唐娜
- Hello? - Donna.
如果哈维在公司  帮我个忙
If Harvey's there, do me a favor--
小点声  别告诉他是我打过来的
keep your voice down, and don't tell him it's me.
迈克  怎么了
Mike, what's going on?
我不会接受那份协议的  唐娜
I'm not taking the deal, Donna.
你疯了吗
Are you crazy?
事情没那么简单
It's not that simple.
什么没那么简单  哈维说如果你
What's not simple about it? Harvey said that if you--
我不在乎哈维是怎么说的
I don't care what Harvey said.
因为他没告诉你们的是
Because what he didn't say
如果我按他的吩咐做了而被人发现了的话
is that if I do what he wants and someone finds out,
那我可能永远也回不到瑞秋身边了
then I may never get back to Rachel at all.
哈维是绝对不会让他们发现的
Harvey would never let them find out--
唐娜  听着  我打电话给你
Donna, look, I called you
是因为我不想和他争论这件事
so that I didn't want to have this argument with him.
我时间不多了
Now, I don't have much time.
你到底要不要帮我
Are you gonna do this for me or not?
我会和他说的
I'll tell him.
那么我还需要你帮我跟他说点别的
Then I also need you to tell him something else for me.
如果他要跑过来试图改变我的想法
If he comes here to try to change my mind,
我是不会见他的
I'm not gonna see him.
你介意告诉我到底是谁说你可以在不知会
You mind telling me who the hell said
我们的情况下抛售南森・巴恩斯的股票的吗
you can dump Nathan Burns' stock without talking to us?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
南森・巴恩斯是谁
Who's Nathan Burns?
外达因能源公司的首席执行官
CEO of Exodyne.
那位南森・巴恩斯啊
Oh, that Nathan Burns.
那样的话  我要说我可以抛售那些股票
In that case, I said I could sell that stock
因为它们归我所有
because I own it.
就是这个  这个  还有这个都归我所有一样
Just like I own this one and this one and this one.
瞧瞧  我的纽宝客投资股价
Look at that, my Neubacher Capital position's
正在暴涨了
going through the roof.
你心知肚明  你跟哈维之间不是这样约定的
That's not the deal you made with Harvey and you know it.
这就是复杂又庞大的华尔街生活
Welcome to the big, bad world of Wall Street.
你是有事要谈  还是我可以继续工作了
Now, do you want something or can I get back to work?
我有事要谈
I want something.
你要解除那笔交易并买回那些股份
You're going to unwind that sale and buy those shares back.
溢价发行  想都别想
At a premium? Not gonna happen.
我是你的房东
I'm your landlord.
然而你之所以出于无奈把办公室租给我
And the fact you had to lease to me
就是因为你们没什么生意
means you don't have much of an operation.
听我说  你这个蠢货
You listen to me, you little pissant.
你根本不知道自己在跟谁打交道
You don't know who you're messing with.
那为何不让我自己来了解
Then why don't I find out?
通过晚餐来了解
Over dinner?
开什么玩笑
You've got to be kidding me.
你把让我跟你共进晚餐
You want me to have dinner with you
作为你退出交易的条件
in exchange for backing off that trade?
我认为只有你想跟我共进晚餐
I think of it as you get to have dinner with me
我才会考虑是否会退出交易
and I choose to back off that trade
因为我很厉害
'cause I am a standup guy.
有些话要跟你说清楚  斯图
Well, let me let you in on a little something there, Stu.
我不会和要挟我的人共进晚餐
I don't share dinner staring down the barrel of a shotgun.
所以你还是先退出交易再来约我吃饭吧
So why don't you unwind that trade and then ask me out?
然后我们就会知道
And then we'll see if you're as charming
你究竟是否像你说得那样魅力十足
as you like to think you are.
我很有魅力
You know what? I am charming.
但我不是个傻子
But I'm not an idiot.
不让我尝到甜头
And I'm not unwinding my trade
我是不会退出交易的
without getting something in return.
哈维  我有事要跟你谈
Harvey, I need to talk to you about something
但这事会让你很反感
and you're not going to like it.
关于什么
About what?
我刚才跟迈克通了电话
That was Mike on the phone before.
那你怎么没叫我
Why didn't you get me?
他不打算接受交易了  哈维
He's not taking the deal, Harvey.
他敢
The hell he isn't.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
去他监狱
To that prison.
哈维  他之所以把电话打给了我而不是你
Harvey, the reason he called me and not you
就是因为他知道你不会同意他拒绝交易的
is because he knew you wouldn't take no for an answer.
我的确不同意
And I'm not going to.
因此他跟我说  如果你去监狱
Which is why he said if you show up there,
他是不会走出牢房见你的
he's not gonna leave his cell.
那就把瑞秋叫来
Then get me Rachel.
不  哈维  你不能告诉她
No, no, Harvey, you cannot tell her.
为什么不能
Like hell I can't.
她是唯一能说服他的人
She's the only one who can convince him.
如果你告诉她  迈克不接受
If you tell her that Mike's not taking a deal
能让他出狱的交易
that can get him out,
她会因此崩溃的
it'll tear her apart.
但如果我不告诉她
And if I don't tell her,
他就还要多坐两年牢
he's gonna be in there for two more years.
这难道是她想要的结果吗
Is that what she wants?
那是他们之间的事
That's between them.
因此我才想告诉她
That's why I want to tell her.
她就会做出权衡
She'll make it between them.
哈维
Harvey.
真可恶  他只是跟这家伙下过盘棋
God damn it, he plays checkers with this guy
就觉得自己的命是人家给的了
and thinks he owes him his life.
不  你明知道这么说对他很不公平
No, that's not fair and you know it,
要不是迈克忠心耿耿  现在坐牢的就是你了
because Mike's loyalty is the reason you're not in prison.
这才是让我最痛不欲生的  唐娜
That's what's killing me, Donna,
你不明白吗
don't you understand?
他去替我坐牢
He's in there instead of me
还要面对一个被我弄进监狱的人
with a guy I put away,
因此当他有机会能出狱时
and I can't just sit here doing nothing
我不能在一旁坐视不管
when he has a chance to get out.
所以你才得想个别的办法出来
Which is why you have to think of something else.
因为一旦你把这事告诉瑞秋
Because if you tell Rachel about this,
那么迈克出狱后的生活...
the life that's waiting for Mike when he gets out...
就不会那么美好了
it isn't going to be there.
哈维  居然这么快又见面了
Harvey. I'm surprised to see you here so soon.
我没想到你这么快就说服了他
I didn't think you'd turn him this fast.
我需要更多的时间
I need more time.
我想你还是没明白我的意思
I don't think you understand.
我正顶着被派去调查其他案件的压力
I'm being pressured to move to another investigation.
给你24小时让他改变主意不然一切免谈
You've got 24 hours to change his mind or this thing is done.
那我需要你帮我办件事
Then I need you to do something for me.
我现在就是在帮你办事
I am doing something for you.
我在想办法让迈克出狱
I'm getting Mike out of prison.
你要帮我办点别的事
Well, you need to do something else for me
否则这事成不了
or that's never gonna happen.
你这话什么意思
What are you talking about?
我想让你去跟他谈
I need you to get into a room with him
因为他听不进去我的话
because he won't listen to what I have to say.
你到底想让我跟他说什么
What exactly do you want me to tell him
还有什么是你没跟他说的
that you haven't already?
肖恩  迈克愿意当老好人
Sean, Mike's a bleeding heart.
你要让他亲自了解这个案子
You need to make the case directly to him.
不管这人干了什么  你得让他看到受害者
He needs to see the victims of whatever the hell this guy did.
这主意不错  哈维
That's a swell idea, Harvey,
但如果有人发现我去了那监狱
but if I go into that prison and someone sees me,
不仅我们会陷入绝境
not only are we dead in the water,
同时迈克的性命也会变得一文不值
but Mike's life isn't worth shit.
你以为这些道理我不明白吗
You think I don't know that?
这道理我都不懂  我还来干什么
What the hell do you think I'm doing here?
什么意思
What are you talking about?
我有个计划
I have a plan.
但你不会喜欢这计划的
But you're not gonna like it.
为什么
Why not?
因为我想让你再找层关系
Because I need you to pull another string,
并且要在弗兰克・加洛
and I need you to do it before
想出别的招数对付迈克之前完成
Frank Gallo tries something else with Mike.
好了  冒牌律师
All right, fake lawyer.
检验你本事的时刻到了
Let's see what you got.
你想让我帮你查查看吗
You're gonna let me look into it for you?
调查  才不是
Look into it? Shit.
你要履行承诺  把我弄出狱
You're gonna get me out of here like you promised.
我从没保证过
I never promised.
我说的是你有一个绝佳机会
I said there was an excellent chance
-可以...  -六周  哥们
- that you could get-- - Six weeks, brother.
我会数日子的
I'll be counting the days.
明天一早我就提交动议
I'll file the motion first thing in the morning.
小子很机灵嘛
There you go.
这就对了
That's what I'm talking about.
我要是发现你在搞我
And if I find out you're screwing me on any level,
你最好在监狱里的某个黑暗角落打个洞
you better hole up in some dark corner of this prison,
祈祷不会被我捉到
pray to God I don't find your ass.
什么情况
What was that all about?
看来他最终还是接受了我的提议
Looks like he took me up on my offer after all.
该死  格蕾琴  她到底在哪
God damn it, Gretchen, where the hell is she?
谁到底在哪
Where the hell is who?
那个你要联系的建筑师
That architect you were supposed to call.
她还要半个小时才到
She's not supposed to be here for another half hour.
如果是我要跟某人做生意
And if I want someone's business,
我至少会提前半个小时到
I show up a half-hour early at the latest.
那你到底要我怎么解决
And what exactly are you looking to have me do
你的小难题
about your little conundrum?
我要你打给她
I want you to give her a call
告诉她如果她连早点赴约的基本礼节
and tell her if she doesn't have the goddamn common courtesy
都不知道
to show up early,
干脆就别来了
then she might as well not show up at all.
-利特先生  -我...
- Mr. Litt. - I--
-你是  -我是塔拉・梅瑟
- Y-yes? - I'm Tara Messer.
我是来商讨你们的改建需求的
I'm here to discuss your remodel needs.
我的需求吗
My needs?
抱歉  本将被我们任聘的建筑师小姐
Well, I'm sorry, Ms. Was-Going-to-Be-Our-Architect.
我们不需要你的服务了
We no longer need your service.
格蕾琴  冷静
Gretchen, calm down.
你反应这么强烈  就像个疯女人一样
You are overreacting like a crazy woman.
你被聘请了
You're hired.
是吗
I am?
是的  你就是合适人选
Oh, yeah. You're right for the job.
我可以感觉到
I can feel it.
你是那里有感觉吧  呵呵
You can feel something, all right.
那先说说你想要
Then why don't we start with
什么样的空间风格吧
what you're looking for in the space?
空间
Space.
对  就是空间
Right, the space. Exactly.
我想在我们和承租人的办公室之间
What I'm looking for are clear yet unobtrusive boundaries
划一条清晰但又不突兀的界限
between our offices and the tenants'.
这个界限得高雅自然
But it needs to be elegant and organic
不然还不如不弄
or we might as well not do it at all.
我知道了
I understand.
就像一首动听的歌剧  无缝自然地
Like the perfect aria leading seamlessly
进入那必然的尾声一样
to its inevitable cadenza.
你是歌剧爱好者吗
You're an opera lover?
仅次于芭蕾
Second only to the ballet.
那我们先结婚吧
Then I suggest we start with a marriage.
我是说参观
I mean a tour.
抱歉  邓巴教授
Excuse me, Professor Dunbar.
您有时间吗
Do you have a moment?
这是教员休息室  赞恩小姐
This is the faculty lounge, Ms. Zane.
你不能到这里来
You're not supposed to be in here.
我知道  我也很抱歉
I understand that, and I'm sorry.
只是这件事很重要  而您又不在办公室
It's just this is important and you weren't in your office.
有什么事
What can I do for you?
我昨天和伦纳德・贝利见面了
I met with Leonard Bailey yesterday.
-他是那个死囚犯  -我知道他是谁
- He's the inmate on death-- - I know who he is.
-有问题吗  -有
- Is there a problem? - Yes, there is.
他被关到了死囚区  但他是无辜的
He's rotting on death row for a crime that he didn't commit.
你才见他十分钟
So you met with him for ten minutes
你就准备放了他吗
and you're ready to release him?
不  我的意思是
No, what I'm saying is--
你只是一个二年级法学生  瑞秋
You're a second-year law student, Rachel.
我叫你加入
I asked you to be a part of this
是因为你是我最聪明的学生之一
because you're one of my brightest students,
但是我特别叫你加入的原因
but I also asked you in particular
是我认为你不是一个如此天真的人
because I didn't think you'd be so naive.
什么
Excuse me?
你的工作不是跟贝利先生谈过一次后
Your job wasn't to talk to Mr. Bailey once
就被他的悲伤故事所动容
and, after being moved by his tale of woe,
然后就把他的案子放在最前面
tell me to jump him to the top of the pile.
你要做的是评估案件  并提供证据
It was to assess his case and present evidence.
我现在就是在这样做啊
And that's exactly what I'm doing here.
我刚把两箱教科书式的起诉不当文件
I just left two boxes of textbook prosecutorial misconduct
交给你的秘书了
with your secretary.
你在昨天一天之内收集到的吗
You found all of that since yesterday?
是啊  我或许只是个法学二年级生
Yes, because while I may only be a second-year law student,
但是我已经当过八年的法律助理了
I have been a practicing paralegal for the past eight years.
这么说  我有很多东西要看了啊
Looks like I have some reading to do.
抱歉打扰您了
I'm sorry for interrupting your day.
午安  赞恩小姐
Good afternoon, Ms. Zane.
午安  教授
Good afternoon, Professor.
那我们就用已有的玻璃图案
And then we use the glass motif you already have
来隔开你们和他们的空间
to partition their space from yours
就从那边那堵墙开始
starting at that wall over there.
没有人会发现它们是隔开的
And no one ever knows they're two separate entities.
如果我们用磨砂玻璃
And if we use the frosted glass,
你根本就不会看到他们
you'll never even have to lay eyes on them.
还有件事
Well, there's just one more thing.
你想知道
You want to know
我是否能给你这边再设计一个大办公室吗
if I can design another bullpen area for your side.
毕竟  那是这个地方的灵魂
After all, it's the heart and soul of the space.
这都猜得到
You get that?
这是我的工作要求
It's my job to get that.
我不懂
I don't understand.
对我来说  建筑不仅仅关乎设计
To me, architecture isn't just about design.
还要求我和客户
It's--it's about connecting with my clients
建立亲密的关系
on an intimate level.
那你真是太擅长了
Well, you're very good at it.
真是太遗憾了
And you know, it's too bad
你已经转租给别人
you already sublet to someone else.
我们也希望扩展来着
We're looking to expand ourselves.
这个地方真是太合适了
This space would have been perfect.
-你说真的吗  -当然
- Are you serious? - Yeah.
实际上  太完美了
In fact, it's so perfect,
我可能会当场就给你报价
I would have made you an offer on the spot.
不论如何  我会尽快做出一些草图的
Anyway, I'll have some plans drawn up as soon as I can.
-我们得赶走那些交易员  -你说什么
- We need to get rid of those traders. - Excuse me?
我不管你和哈维与他们达成了
I don't care what kind of deal
怎样的协议
you and Harvey cut with them.
我们得把他们赶走
We need to get rid of them
而且必须现在就赶走
and we need to do it now.
路易  我不会这么做的
Well, Louis, I'm not going to do that
反正无论我们把他们换成谁
because whoever we replace them with,
这种事情总是会再发生
this conversation is just going to happen again.
因为你我心里都清楚  你已经疯了
Because we both know that you're out of your mind.
不会再发生的
It's not gonna happen again
因为在这件事上  我很清醒
because in this particular case, I am not out of my mind.
你为什么要我这么做呢
Why do you want me to do this?
因为我爱上了一个建筑师
Because I'm in love with an architect.
来让我先搞清楚状况
Let me get this straight.
你要我对那些已经和我开战的人们
You want me to further antagonize people
展开更进一步的对抗
that I'm already fighting with
就因为你没胆量
because you don't have the balls
约一个女人出来
to ask a woman out on a date?
你也可以这么理解
That's one way of looking at it.
不  还有一个角度
No, there's another way.
-我不答应  -无所谓
- The answer is no. - Okay, fine.
我按原计划进行就好了
I'll just stick to the original plan
让她整个重新设计我们的办公室
of having her completely redesign our space,
而且我会保证她的工期能够
and I'll just make sure it takes long enough
长到让她能够疯狂地爱上我
for her to fall madly in love with me,
反正不会超过两三年
and it shouldn't take more than two or three years.
路易  你一字一句给我听清楚
Louis, I want you to look at me when I say this.
如果你雇这个女人
If you hire this woman to do anything
来做和公司办公室相关的任何事情
relating to this firm's space,
我会亲自把你从楼顶上扔下去
I will personally throw you off the roof this building.
明白了吗
Is that clear?
-也就是说你会至少考虑一下吗  -出去
- So you'll think about it? - Get out.
阿诺
Ahnold.
来  看看你有什么料
Come on. Let's see what you got.
我不知道你之前玩过
I didn't know you played.
之前玩过  屁啦
Played? Shit.
我破过P.S. 092单场得分纪录
I set the P.S. 092 single-game scoring record.
P.S. 092是个小学啊  哥们儿
P.S. 092 is an elementary school, my friend.
对  六年级  我掌控全场
Yeah, sixth grade. I dominated.
听说你要帮加洛的假释提交动议
Heard you had to file that motion for Gallo's parole.
-提交了  -已经提交了
- I did. - Already?
不过是个十八页的判决修正而已
It was an 18-page sentencing amendment.
我睡着觉都能弄好
I could do that in my sleep.
那么高效  得让你帮我干活才行
I should get you to do some work for me.
为什么  你需要我吗
Why? You need some?
还没  但是如果我需要的话
No, but if I did, I'd probably get myself a lawyer
也会找个监狱外面的律师
who didn't sleep in a prison.
你没事吧
You all right?
我不知道
I don't--I don't know.
什么叫我不知道
What do you mean, you don't know?
究竟怎么了  你的胃怎么了吗
What is it, your stomach?
天  不太对劲
my God, something's not right.
深呼吸
Take a deep breath.
低下头
Put your head down.
天啊  不行  没用的
God, I can't-- that's not gonna do anything.
我想
I think...
天啊  我想有人对我
My God, I think somebody
动手脚了
did something to me.
快来帮忙
Can I get some help over here?
警卫
Guard!
迈克  和我说话
Mike, talk to me.
是加洛做的
It's Gallo.
他肯定动了手脚  在我的
Yeah, he must've put something in my--
快来帮忙  警卫
Somebody do something! Guard!
打电话给哈维
Call Harvey.
警卫
Guard!
迈克  迈克
Mike. Mike!
他在哪里
Where is he?
如果我知道你说的是谁  或许我可以
If I knew who you were talking about, maybe I could--
迈克・罗斯  我现在就要见他
Mike Ross. I need to see him right now.
你是
And who are you?
哈维・斯佩克特  他的律师
Harvey Specter. I'm his attorney.
罗斯先生现在在医务室里
Mr. Ross is in the infirmary,
然而你不能去那里见他
but you can't see him in there.
那就把典狱长给我找来
Then get me the warden.
我不喜欢别人逼着做事  斯佩克特先生
I don't appreciate being pushed around, Mr. Specter.
我不关心
I don't care.
我想要全世界都知道今天这儿发生了什么
I want everyone to know what happened here today.
发生的事情他们都看到了
They saw what happened.
看到和知道还是有区别的
Yeah, there's a difference between seeing and knowing.
你是凯文・米勒
You Kevin Miller?
你是谁
Who are you?
哈维・斯佩克特
Harvey Specter.
迈克・罗斯的律师
I'm Mike Ross's lawyer.
我已经告诉典狱长
Look, I already told the warden
我没看到任何人动了他的食物
I didn't see anyone touch his food.
你看到过弗兰克・加洛和他在一起吗
Did you see Frank Gallo with him?
看到还是没看到
Did you or didn't you?
你这是要害死我吗
Are you trying to get me killed, man?
他动了他的食物没
Did he touch his food or not?
好吧  他动了  昨晚晚餐的时候
Yeah, he did, last night at dinner.
但是迈克提议帮加洛假释
But Mike offered to get Gallo parole
加洛也答应了  为什么还要加害于他
and Gallo took him up on it, so why would he poison him?
因为他并没有真的答应迈克
Because he didn't really take Mike up on that offer.
他答应只是为了接近他
He just did it to get close to him.
或者是为了让迈克知道如果他出不去
Or he did it to give Mike a taste of what happens
究竟会发生什么
if he doesn't come through.
无论怎样  你离那个混蛋远点
Either way, you stay the hell away from that son of a bitch.
好了  够了  我们走吧
All right, that's enough. Let's go.
律师
Counselor!
我听说你家小孩在院子里犯了个小胃痛
I heard your boy had a little tummy ache out in the yard.
你个人渣
You piece of shit.
你居然下毒害他
You goddamn poisoned him.
警卫  把他弄走
Guards, get him out of here.
我什么也没做
I didn't do shit.
你怎么不过来站在我面前说
Why don't you come over here and say that to my face?
-你以为我不敢吗  -真该死
- You think I won't? - God damn it.
我说了把他带回牢房
I said get him back to his cell!
这可不包括在我们说好的事情里
This wasn't part of the deal.
我们说好让你来见他的同屋狱友
We talked about you seeing his roommate,
而不是去招惹弗兰克・加洛
not rushing Frank Gallo.
我的人还躺在医疗室昏迷不醒
Yeah,  my guy's lying unconscious in the infirmary.
去告我啊
So sue me.
你怎么知道加洛会上钩
How did you know Gallo would take the bait?
因为他是畜生  畜生总是会咬钩上当的
Because he's an animal, and animals always take the bait.
我真欣赏你能看清事情走向
I'll give you credit for knowing how it would go down.
我不需要称赞
I don't need credit.
我需要知道迈克・罗斯在哪
I need to know where Mike Ross is.
在我被告知带他去的地方
Where I was instructed to put him.
我得跟你说  斯佩克特先生
Let me tell you something, Mr. Specter,
我不了解你
I don't know you.
所以以防你想耍别的花招
So in case you're thinking of trying anything,
我们在那个孩子的腿上安了监测器
that kid has a monitor on his leg,
如果监测器失联哪怕一秒钟
and if it goes dark for even one second,
我保证到时你会和他一起坐牢
I'm gonna make sure that you end up in a cell here with him.
不会出问题的
It's not gonna go dark,
他会按我之前说的时间回来的
and he'll be back here when I said he would.
那之后  我也可以保证
Then after that, I'm gonna make sure
他会永远地离开这里
he gets out of here. For good.
你感觉怎么样
How you feeling?
什么情况
What's going on?
我在哪
Where am I?
你在我车里
You're in the back of my car.
你被下药了
You were drugged.
加洛干的
By Gallo.
我干的
By me.
什么
What?
卡荷尔让典狱长和狱医
Cahill got the warden and the prison doctor
往你食物里加了些东西
to put something in your food.
整件事只有他们知道
They're the only ones who know what's going on.
你到底在说什么呢
What the hell are you talking about?
我们需要你改变心意  去接受这个交易
We needed to change your mind about taking this deal,
而只要你在里面  我们就做不到
and we couldn't do it as long as you're in there.
我的天哪
Jesus Christ.
那你就给我下药
So you drugged me?
要让你不在牢里  我们就要一个好理由
We needed a cover for why you're not in your cell,
这是唯一可行的办法了
and this was the only way to do it.
你疯了吗
Are you insane?
你这是带我越狱啊
You broke me out of prison?
我可没有带你越任何地方
I didn't break you out of anywhere.
这是卡荷尔批准的
Cahill sanctioned it.
要说有人疯了  那也是你
And if anyone's insane, it's you, 'cause you're the one
因为是你拒绝了出狱的机会
turning down a chance to get out of that place.
但我们现在没时间讨论那件事
But we don't have time to talk about that right now.
卡荷尔在等我们
Cahill's waiting for us.
你把我弄出来就是为了带我去见卡荷尔
You got me out to see Cahill?
我只是说他在等我们
I said he's waiting.
我又没说我要带你去他那
I didn't say that's where I'm taking you.
那你到底要带我去哪
Then where the hell are you taking me?
你认为我和瑞秋一起待几个小时
You think me spending a couple of hours with Rachel
就能改变心意
is gonna change my mind?
如果这都不行  那你肯定有毛病
If it doesn't, there's something wrong with you.
那么  你是要对我大吼大叫
So, you gonna yell at me?
还是抓住这唯一的机会
Or you gonna take the only chance you're gonna get
能够在接下来的两年里
to be alone with the woman you love
和你爱的女人待在一起
for the next two years?
拜托告诉我你没有跟瑞秋提过
Please tell me that you did not tell her
卡荷尔的提议
about Cahill's offer.
我倒是想啊
I wanted to.
但是你得谢谢唐娜  是她拦住了我
But you have Donna to thank for the fact that I didn't.
我该怎么跟瑞秋解释我出现在这里
What am I supposed to tell Rachel about why I'm here?
如果是我  我就告诉她真相
If it were me, I'd tell her the truth.
现在  既然你不想那么做
Now, since you don't want to do that,
你真幸运我还想到了别的说辞
you're lucky I came up with something else.
等涨到三十就卖掉
Wait till it hits 30 and then sell.
看这谁来了
Look who it is.
你准备改变主意接受我的提议了吗
You change your mind about my offer?
我现在还不会考虑
I'm not there just yet.
但我确实是来道歉的
But I did come to apologize.
我并不是想表现的那么好斗
I didn't mean to be so combative before.
你是个自尊心强的女人  我懂  都过去了
You're a proud woman. I understand. Bygones.
你把这里经营的很出色
You know, your operation here is kind of impressive.
介意我看一下吗
Mind if I look at one?
你想看什么就看什么
You can take a look at anything of mine you want.
那一行是什么意思
Now, what does that line right there mean?
怎么搞的  那是我的纽宝客投资公司股价
What the hell, that's my Neubacher Capital position.
好像跌的很快
It seems to be falling very quickly.
是好事吗
Is that a good thing?
是你干的
You did this.
我不知道你在说什么
I'm not sure what you mean.
我所做的只是下午
All I did this afternoon
给我在雅格森・科尔尼工作的朋友打了个电话
was call my friend at Jacobson Kearney
让他们发布一个新闻稿
and have them issue a press release
披露他们客户的公司合并谈判
about their client's merger negotiations.
我又怎么会知道这会
I mean, how was I supposed to know that it would make
让你的纽宝客投资公司股价暴跌
your Neubacher position fall through the floor?
你利用了我昨天给你的信息
You used the information I gave you yesterday
那是关于我控股股份的  所以你知道
about my holdings, that's how.
那属于内部消息  我能证实
That's inside information, and I can prove it.
不会的  本来是可以的
No, it could have been,
可惜你的律师在要求截止日十天前
if your attorney hadn't filed your position with the SEC
就把你的持仓在证监会备了案
ten days earlier than he had to.
我会记住这件事的
I'm not gonna forget this.
很好  因为我经营的时间
Good, because my operation's been around
比你经营的时间长的多
a hell of a lot longer than yours,
我们可以成为朋友  当然也可能成为敌人
and we can be friends or we can be enemies.
但如果你再给我找麻烦
But you mess with me again
我就不只是把你踢出这里
and I'll not only kick you out of these offices,
我会整死你
I'll put you in the ground.
瑞秋
Rachel.
你怎么来了
How?
哈维
Harvey.
我不懂
I don't understand.
我知道你知道弗兰克・加洛的事
I know you know about Frank Gallo.
但你不知道的是
But what you don't know
他们关了我三十六小时单独监禁
is that they put me in solitary confinement for 36 hours.
-天呐  -没事的
- Oh my God. - It's okay.
我很安全
I was safe.
后来哈维让他们看了监控
Then Harvey made them watch the video,
录像表明我只是正当防卫
which showed that I was only defending myself.
他们也很高兴能以六个小时时间
Turns out they were more than happy to trade
和一个追踪器的代价避免一场诉讼
six hours and an ankle bracelet to avoid a lawsuit.
我们只有六小时
We only have six hours?
是的  我一秒钟也不想浪费
Yeah, and I don't want to waste any of it.
利特先生  你这是
Mr. Litt, what are you--
请别这么见外  叫我路易吧
Please, call me Louis.
有什么事情吗  路易
What can I do for you, Louis?
塔拉  恐怕我有坏消息告诉你
Tara, I'm afraid I have some bad news.
我们最终还是不能
We're not gonna be moving forward
继续改建项目了
with the renovations after all.
真遗憾
I'm sorry to hear that.
不  这和你没关系
No, it has nothing to do with you.
当然  我会个人出资
And of course I will pay you out of my own pocket
为你所做的一切工作付钱
for any of the work you've already done.
没有这个必要
That won't be necessary.
请别客气  塔拉  我一定得付
Please, Tara, I insist.
既然如此  那我不如也给你看看
In that case, I might as well at least
我的初步设计吧
show you what I had in mind.
你能看出  这只是初步草图
As you can see, these are just rough drawings.
我觉得很好了
Not to me.
这是一个优雅的S形弯曲的磨砂玻璃
Here's the frosted glass wall curving in an elegant "S"
用以隔开空间
that separates the space.
好美
It's beautiful.
这还不是最棒的
That's not even the best part.
因为我知道新的大办公室对你多重要
Because I know how important the new bullpen is to you,
所以我以费城的金美儿中心为原型
I modeled it after the Kimmel Center in Philadelphia,
整个空间周围是
and I enclosed the entire space--
桃花心木
In mahogany.
如果能实现肯定非常漂亮
It would have been exquisite.
但有些事注定无缘
But some things weren't meant to be.
是啊
Yeah.
你愿意整修我在汉普顿的
How would you feel about renovating my summer house
避暑别墅吗
in the Hamptons?
我很感激
I appreciate the thought,
路易  但我不接受私宅的工作
Louis, but I don't do residential work.
不是私宅  那是我的家庭办公室
It's not residential. I use it as a home office.
但那肯定很小吧
But it would be so small.
不  我希望把整栋房子
No, I want the entire house to be
做成公司的分部
a satellite division of the firm.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
我这辈子从来没有这么确定过
I've never been as sure of anything in my entire life.
那我很期待与你合作  路易
Then I look forward to working with you, Louis.
肖恩  有什么事吗
Sean, what can I do for you?
-他们人呢  -什么
- Where the hell are they? - What?
我在我的办公室
I've been sitting in my office
等了他们两小时了
for two hours waiting for them.
他们在哪
Where the hell are they?
我不知道  也许是堵车了
I don't know. Maybe they're caught in traffic.
听着  我可以联系监狱
Listen to me, I can contact the prison
直接找出他们的位置
and find out exactly where they are.
但如果那样做  会掀起一场
But I do that, it starts a tornado of shit
以你的上司为中心的风暴
with your boss in the eye of the storm.
所以你最好马上告诉我
So you're gonna tell me right now
他们到底要干什么
what the hell they're up to.
他在迈克的公寓外面等他呢
He's waiting for Mike outside of his apartment.
等他做什么
Waiting for him to do what?
-他和瑞秋在一起  -你逗我呢吧
- He's with Rachel. - You got to be kidding me.
我找了那么多关系不是为了让迈克・罗斯
I didn't pull in every favor I have so Mike Ross
享受什么夫妻探访的
could have some conjugal visit.
对  你找了那么多关系
No, you pulled in every favor you had
是为了让哈维说服迈克去做你想做的事
so that Harvey could convince Mike to do what you wanted
这就能达到这个目的
and this is gonna make that happen.
就是给他找个女人吗
By getting him laid?
是提醒他如果不接受你的条件
By reminding him of what he's missing out on
他会错过什么
if he doesn't take your deal.
计划不是这样的
That wasn't the plan.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
我要去找他
I'm gonna go down there and do
按我们的原计划来
what we said we were gonna do.
我要给迈克讲因为那个混蛋
I'm gonna show Mike the innocent people
失去了一切的无辜的人的事
that lost everything because of that bastard.
肖恩  拜托  如果你那么做
Sean, please, if you do that,
瑞秋就会知道一切了
Rachel will find out about everything
-我们不能让她知道  -为什么
- and that can't happen. - Why not?
因为迈克已经放弃她选择了一次监狱
Because Mike chose prison over her once,
要是他再这样做一次  她不会原谅他的
and if he does it again, she'll never forgive him.
那是迈克的事  不是我的
Mike's problem. Not mine.
不是你的  但是哈维的
No, that's Harvey's problem.
他答应了迈克不会告诉她
He promised Mike he wouldn't tell her,
哈维是很重承诺的
and Harvey's a man of his word.
他要是重承诺  现在人就应该在这里
If he were a man of his word, he would be here right now.
那你要干什么
So what are you gonna do?
我要去做本来就应该
I'm gonna do what should've been done
做的事
in the first place.
告诉迈克的未婚妻
I'm gonna tell Mike's fiancée
他本有机会出来
that he has a chance to get out
但他自己不愿意
but he doesn't want to take it.
打算告诉我这都是什么情况吗
You want to tell me what that was all about?
哈维和卡荷尔把迈克弄出了监狱
Harvey and Cahill got Mike out of prison
为了说服他接受交易
to convince him to take the deal,
哈维带迈克去了瑞秋家  没去见肖恩
and Harvey brought Mike to Rachel instead of to Sean.
他竟然带迈克越了狱
He broke Mike out of prison?
他疯了吗
Is he crazy?
我刚开始得知也觉得疯狂
It sounded crazy to me at first too,
但是哈维一直困在害迈克进监狱的愧疚里
but Harvey's living with the guilt of putting Mike in there
卡荷尔又愿意帮忙  你能怪他吗
and Cahill was willing to do it, so can you blame him?
不能
No. I can't.
但我要知道事情的结果
But I want to know how this whole thing shakes out.
我今晚就要知道
And I want to know tonight.
现在几点
What time is it?
我们还有时间
We still have time.
天呐
My God.
我睡着了
I fell asleep.
是的
You did.
怎么不叫醒我
Why didn't you wake me?
因为你看起来好平和
Because you looked so peaceful.
瑞秋  我不希望我们浪费...
Rachel, I don't want us to waste--
我们什么也没有浪费
We're not wasting anything.
迈克  我不知道你在里面睡得怎么样
Mike, I don't know how well you sleep in there,
所以能让你睡一觉...
so to be able to give you this...
谢谢你
Thank you.
我能给你做点什么吃的
Can I cook you something?
你想吃什么我都给你做
I'll make you anything you want.
不  我只想跟你一起躺着  看着对方
No, I just want us to lie here and stare at each other.
什么也不说
Not saying anything.
天呐
God.
你好美
You're so beautiful.
我以为你想要我们保持安静呢
I thought you wanted us to be quiet.
我忍不住嘛
Couldn't help it.
你总是跟我说我有多好看
You know, you always tell me how beautiful I am.
我却从没机会告诉你在我眼里
You never give me a chance to tell you how handsome
你有多帅
I think you are.
我以为你爱的是我的思想
I thought you loved me for my mind.
没错
I do.
但那不代表
But that doesn't mean
我不能同时认为你长得帅
that I don't also think you're handsome.
迈克  怎么了
Mike, what's going on?
我得跟你说件事
There's something I need to tell you.
跟你能在这里的真实原因有关吗
Does it have something to do with why you're really here?
因为我不相信你之前说的话
Because I didn't believe what you told me earlier.
那你怎么什么都没说
Why didn't you say something?
因为你在这儿了  我什么都不在乎了
Because you're here, so I didn't care.
怎么了
What's that?
我会买回南森・巴恩斯公司的股票
I'm unwinding my position with Nathan Burns' company.
我很感激
I appreciate that.
但我不需要把文件都带回家
But I don't need to take home the paper trail.
这不是文件
It's not a paper trail.
是份聘书
It's an engagement letter.
我发现我的律师在必要时间之前
Turns out my attorney was filing my positions
就上报了我的持仓
before he had to,
我就把他开了
so I let him go.
你想让我签你做客户
You want me to take you as a client.
你愿意的话
If you'll have me.
就一个条件
On one condition.
我听说你在拿路易・利特取乐
I hear you've been having fun with Louis Litt.
到此为止
But it stops now.
成交
Done.
我就该知道一个雇了那种骗子的人
I should have known the guy who hired a fraud like that
是会耍这种花招的
would pull a stunt like this.
这花招可以帮你拿到你想要的
This stunt is gonna get youexactly what you want.
不  哈维
No, Harvey.
我要去把事实告诉那小子的未婚妻
I'm gonna get what I want
让她帮我做事
by telling that kid's fiancée the truth
来拿到我想要的
and letting her do the work for me.
听我说  肖恩
Listen to me, Sean.
她不知道
She doesn't know
是因为他不想让她知道
because he doesn't want her to know.
我不管他想要什么
I don't give a shit what he wants.
那你相信我  这是唯一让你
Then trust me, this is the only way
如愿以偿的办法
to get what you want.
信你  你当我的面骗我
Trust you? You lied to my face.
我做了判断
I made a judgment call.
那你看着我的眼睛
Then look me in the eye
告诉我你做这个判断
and tell me you didn't make that call
是在你要求我把他弄出来之后
before you asked me to get him out.
我就知道
I knew it.
你一直都想把他带到这儿来
The whole time you were always gonna bring him here.
因为这是完成任务的办法
Because this is the way to get it done.
那你为什么一开始不告诉我
Then why didn't you tell me that in the first place?
因为那结果会变成
Because it would have ended up
你想要利用瑞秋
with you wanting to use Rachel.
无论如何结果都是这样了  现在给我让开
It ended there anyway. Now get the hell out of my way.
别逼我阻止你  肖恩
Don't make me stop you, Sean.
你是在威胁一名联邦检察官吗  哈维
Are you threatening a federal prosecutor, Harvey?
没错  我是在威胁你
You're goddamn right I am.
你这次最好比上次
Well, you better think about this move
想得更清楚点
more than you thought about the last one.
因为这次绝对不会让你有好果子吃
'Cause it's not gonnaend well for you.
在我看来
Far as I'm concerned,
这是一回事
it's the same move.
我做了保证  就要守住它
I made a promise and I'm not gonna break it.
哈维
Harvey!
无论你们在吵什么  都可以停了
Whatever you're fighting about, you can stop.
我把一切都告诉瑞秋了
I told Rachel everything.
我接受协议
I'm taking the deal.
那我们就上车走吧
Then let's get in the car and get moving.
*再吻我一次*[Death Valley by My Jerusalem]
*Oh kiss me one more time*
*再吻我一次*
*在太阳下山前*
*Before the sun goes down*
*所有夜行的动物*
*And all the creatures of the night*
*爬过这座城市*
*Crawling over this town*
*我在城中迷失*
*I'm lost in the city*
*这天使之城*
*The city of angels*
*落入谷底*
*Down in the valley*